yeepe.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy - Yeepe.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Personally identifiable information you provide to Yeepe! will not be sold or given to outside sources without your permission. Yeepe! uses the information we collect in order to provide you with personalized services, such as updates and account information. 

**WHY WE OBTAIN INFORMATION**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a new account profile on the site to use specific features available only to registered users. The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to use by not having you enter information more than once. We may also periodically use your information to alert you to updated information and other new services from Yeepe!. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of Yeepe! services. But you will not be able to post or access areas that require registration.

**REGISTERED USER PROFILES**

When you register, your information is protected by use of a password. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password that is neither common nor known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password. If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the "my account" link provided on our system, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on Yeepe!, your information stays with you.

**NOTICE TO PARENTS**

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.
